<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Moments</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Moments</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_memory_layout">addMemoryLayout</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_memory">View Moments</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="colorListArray">
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Green</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="scopeListArray">
        <item>Public</item>
        <item>Private</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Enter Your Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Enter Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="about_text">This application is at it\'s most simplest stage. All you do is click on the pink button, and then type in some text on the next screen. This is now accessible through finding that pin marker on the map. \n \n If you wish to clear all the markers off the map, click the \"Clear All\" button(above), and then restart the application. \n\n If you\'re not seeing the markers, wait a second before hitting refresh, after submitting your moment.</string>
    <string name="about_title">Help Section</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_profile">User Profile</string>
    <string name="privacy_text">Privacy</string>
    <string name="google_string">https://www.google.com/?</string>
    <string name="location_text_string">error getting location</string>
    <string name="public_string">Public</string>
    <string name="private_string">Private</string>
    <string name="remove_image_button_text">Remove Image</string>
    <string name="newfeature">\"Feature Coming Soon\"</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Moments Privacy Policy Last Updated: February 11, 2017 \n\n Protecting your privacy (or the privacy of your authorized child) is really important Moments, Inc. (“Moments,” “we,” “our,” or “us”.) With this in mind, we’re providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information that we receive through our app, which are accessible via our mobile device application (the “App”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party websites, services, or applications, even if they are accessible through any of our Services. \n\n 1. REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY \n\n ANY INFORMATION THAT IS COLLECTED VIA OUR SERVICES IS COVERED BY THE PRIVACY POLICY IN EFFECT AT THE TIME SUCH INFORMATION IS COLLECTED. WE MAY REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME. IF WE MAKE ANY MATERIAL CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING ANY CHANGE THAT WE PROPOSE THAT WILL HAVE RETROACTIVE EFFECT, WE’LL NOTIFY YOU OF THOSE CHANGES BY POSTING THEM ON THE SERVICES OR BY SENDING YOU AN EMAIL OR OTHER NOTIFICATION, AND WE’LL UPDATE THE “LAST UPDATED DATE” ABOVE TO INDICATE WHEN THOSE CHANGES WERE MADE. \n\n 2. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION \n\n a. Information Collected or Received from You. Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services, and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services. \n\n i. Account Information. \n\n During use of the app and when you register to create an account with us (“Account”), we’ll collect certain information that can be used to identify or recognize you (“PII”). Specifically, because you must have an account with Centennial Arts before registering to create an Account, we will collect PII (such as your email address) that your privacy settings with Centennial Arts permit us to access. \n\n b. Information Collected Using Cookies and other Web Technologies. \n\n Like many website owners and operators, we use automated data collection tools such as Cookies and Web Beacons to collect certain information on our Site. \n “Cookies” are small text files that are placed on your hard drive by a Web server when you (or your authorized child) access our Services. We may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies to identify that you (or your authorized child) have logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you (or your authorized child) interact with our Services. We may also use Cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Session Cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close the browser. Persistent Cookies remain on your computer and will identify how you use the Services over time. Although most browsers automatically accept Cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting Cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept Cookies, you (or your authorized child) may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. Some third party services providers that we engage (including third party advertisers) may also place their own Cookies on your hard drive. \n “Web Beacons” (also known as web bugs, pixel tags, or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that may be included on our Services for several purposes. For example, we may use Web Beacons to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to track and measure the performance of our Services, to monitor how many visitors view our Services, and to monitor the effectiveness of our advertising. Unlike Cookies, which are stored on the user’s hard drive, Web Beacons are typically embedded invisibly on web pages (or in an e-mail). \n\n c. Information Related to Use of the Services. \n\n Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as “Log Data”), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a “User”). Log Data may include information such as a User’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, user agent, browser type, operating system, the web page that a User was visiting before accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Services that a User clicked on, and other statistics. We use Log Data to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) Log Data to improve, customize, and enhance our Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s Log Data and other information to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Services are used and use such aggregated information to understand and improve our Services and to administer use of the Services. If we engage a third party to analyze the Log Data, we will ensure that such third party is bound by contractual terms requiring it to process such Log Data in accordance with relevant European data protection laws (including, without limitation, the Data Protection Directive). \n\n d. Information Sent by Your Mobile Device. \n\n We collect certain information that your mobile device sends when you use our Services, like a device identifier, user settings, and the operating system of your device, as well as information about your use of our Services while using the mobile device. We may use this information to provide the Services and to improve and personalize our Services for you. \n\n e. Location Information. \n\n The App is location based. We collect and store information about your location when you use our App and take actions that use the location services made available through your device’s mobile operating system, which makes use of cell/mobile tower triangulation, wifi triangulation, and/or GPS. You understand and agree that by using our App you will be transmitting your device location to us and some of that location information, along with your user name, may be shared through the App. For example, when you take certain actions, your user name and location may be shared through the App with other users who are using the app. We may also use location information to improve and personalize our Services for you. \n\n 3. INFORMATION THAT WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES \n\n We will not share any of your PII that we have collected from or regarding you except as described below: \n\n a. Information Shared with Moments. \n\n If you register to create an Account and any bugs, errors, or other incidents or problems are found in the operation or development of the Services, we may share your PII with Moments if such collaboration is required to investigate, diagnose, correct, and/or resolve the issue. Any information that you provide directly to Moments is subject to the applicable company’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content, privacy, or security practices and policies of Moments. \n\n b. Information Shared with Our Services Providers. \n\n We may engage third party service providers to work with us to administer and provide the Services. These third party service providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf and are expressly obligated to secure your (or your authorized child’s) PII and not to disclose or use your PII for any other purpose. \n\n c. Information Shared with Third Parties. \n\n We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for research and analysis, demographic profiling, and other similar purposes. This information will not include your PII. \n\n d. Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions. \n\n Information that we collect from our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. Thus, if we are acquired by a third party as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition, or asset sale or if our assets are acquired by a third party in the event we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, some or all of our assets, including your (or your authorized child’s) PII, may be disclosed or transferred to a third party acquirer in connection with the transaction. In the event of such a transaction, we will give you notice of the transaction and the opportunity for a period of 30 days to refuse disclosure or transfer of your (or your authorized child’s) PII to the third party acquirer in connection with the transaction. \n\n e. Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others. \n\n We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you that is in our possession or control to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (a) to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas); (b) to protect our property, rights, and safety and the property, rights, and safety of a third party or the public in general; and © to identify and stop any activity that we consider illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity. \n\n 4. YOUR CHOICES \n\n We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your PII and we’ll respect the choices you make. Please note that if you decide not to provide us with the PII that we request, you may not be able to access some or all of the features of the Services. \n\n a. Rescinding Your Consent. \n\n You have the right to refuse further collection, use, and/or disclosure of your PII by notifying us. If you have consented to your access to and use of the Services but wish to rescind such consent, please contact us at kevinsapps12@gmail.com to submit the request. We will promptly discontinue your access to and use of the Services and ensure that your PII is no longer publicly accessible through the Services. Please note, however, that if you refuse further collection, use, and/or disclosure of your PII, you may not be able to access and use all or a portion of the Services. \n\n b. Opt-Out. \n\n For residents of member states of the European Union and Parents of authorized children, if you elect to subscribe to our mailing list during Account registration, we will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote our Services. For all other users, if you do not opt out of subscription to our mailing list during Account registration, we will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote our Services. When you receive such promotional communications from us, you will have the opportunity to opt out (through your Account or by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive). We will need to send you certain communications regarding the Services and you will not be able to opt out of those communications (e.g., communications regarding updates to this Privacy Policy). \n\n c. Accessing, Modifying, and Deleting Your Information. \n\n Parents may request and obtain access to PII stored about their children who are under the age of 13 by contacting us at kevinapps12@gmail.com. If you want us to modify or delete your PII and/or your Account, or discontinue the provision of your PII to third parties, please contact us at kevinsapps12@gmail.com with your request. We’ll take steps to modify or delete your information as soon we can (unless otherwise permitted by applicable law). Please note, however, that some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. \n\n 5. KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION \n\n Following termination or deactivation of your Account, Moments, its clients, affiliates, or service providers may retain information (including your profile information) and user content for a commercially reasonable time period for backup, archival, and/or audit purposes. If you have any questions about termination or deactivation of your Account, please contact us directly at kevinsapps12@gmail.com. \n\n 6. RESPONDING TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS \n\n Our Services do not have the capability to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from various web browsers. To learn more about browser tracking signals and “Do Not Track,” please visit http://allaboutdnt.org. \n\n 7. THE SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION \n\n We take appropriate administrative, physical, and electronic measures designed to protect the information that we collect from or about you from accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss or unauthorized access, use, modification, interference, or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information. \n\n 8. LINKS TO OTHER SITES \n\n Our Services may contain links to websites and services that are owned or operated by third parties (each, a “Third Party Service”). Any information that you provide on or to a Third Party Service or that is collected by a Third Party Service (including Google, Facebook and Moments) is provided directly to the owner or operator of the Third Party Service and is subject to the owner’s or operator’s privacy policy. We’re not responsible for the content, privacy, or security practices and policies of any Third Party Service. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of all Third Party Service that you access via our Services. \n\n 9. International Transfer \n\n Your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you’re located outside the United States and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there. Whenever we transfer your PII outside of the jurisdiction in which you are located, we ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place in relation to its security. You may request us not to transfer your PII to the United States, but if you do so, we may not be able to provide some or all of the Services to you. \n\n 10. Questions? \n\n Please contact us at kevinsapps12@gmail.com if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you wish to make a complaint about our collection, use, or disclosure of your PII under this Privacy Policy. We will use our reasonable endeavors to address any complaint you may have as soon as possible. \n\n</string>
    <!--<string name="upload_image_button_text">Add Image</string>-->
</resources>
